-Previously on Friends....
-I don't feel like I have a girlfriend.
You want me to quit my job so you
can feel like you have a girlfriend?
-ls this about Mark?
-Oh, my God.
-Okay, it's not.
I cannot keep having this
fight with you!
Maybe we should just take a break.
Fine. You're right.
Let's take a break.
Let's get some frozen yogurt
or something.
A break from us.
Then we had this big fight,
and I said I wanted to take a break.
I don't want to take a break.
This is crazy.
Can't we work on this?
What do you want to drink?
Who's that?
Nobody.
Is that Mark?
Honey, look, he just
Yeah. Got it!
Hey, come dance.
What, are you married?
Because that's okay.
How was the big anniversary dinner?
Well, we never actually got to dinner.
Nice.
We kind of broke up instead.
What?
My God!
It's on the ceiling!
That's okay.
This is more important than fruit...
...on my ceiling.
You broke up?
Yeah, but it's okay because
when Ross left, Mark came over.
-Oh, no! You and Mark?
-It's okay. Calm down.
Mark and I talked...
...and I realized how much
I love your stupid brother.
We got our problems,
but I really wanna make it work.
Morning!
The One the Morning After
It's me. I've been trying
to reach you all night. I feel awful.
There's nothing between me and Mark.
This whole breakup thing
is just stupid.
I'm sorry I put you through it.
And I don't want to get
back together over a machine.
So I love you.
I love you.
And you know what?
I'm gonna go to bed now...
...but on my way to work tomorrow,
I'll stop by around 8:30. Bye.
Chloe, how's it coming?
What kind of puppy do you think
I should get?
Well, how about a big one?
-But my apartment's so
-Then a small one.
-We have to go.
-Wait! Where's my shoes?
You need shoes?
-Do I know why we're rushing?
-You know my girlfriend?
It turns out that she wants
to get back together.
I found it!
That's so great for you guys!
You must be so happy!
Yes, I am. One of the many
things I'm feeling.
-Good luck with your girlfriend.
-Thank you.
-You got my message?
-You are right on time!
So can I be your girlfriend again?
Yes, you can. Very much.
-Why are you mopping your ceiling?
-There's banana on it.
I have the spirit of an
old lndian woman living in mine.
So, then, you know.
The mailman was here,
so I brought your mail.
-Oh, good. Thanks.
-Now, what is Fabutech?
Don't judge me too much, okay?
I saw this infomercial,
and I swear I have never...
... bought anything on TV before.
Except for this mop.
But there was this amazing stuff
on leg-waxing
Waxine!
Yes! Have you seen it?
It's incredible!
I want to be a Waxine Girl!
I know!
Do you think it really doesn't hurt?
How can they do that?
Hello! Organic substances recently
discovered in the rain forest?
They have the best stuff in there.
Oh, my God!
We figured when we couldn't find you,
you'd gone to make up with Rachel.
Which is probably what
you should have done.
You think?
God, I'm in hell.
I mean, what am I gonna do?
Rachel's all "I love you,"
and all I can think about...
...is what is she gonna do
when I tell her what I did?
First, we should address
the more important question...
...how dumb are you?
Look, we're trying to
rebuild a relationship here, right?
How can I do that
without being honest?
I'm onboard about
the total-honesty thing. I am.
Just not about stuff that's
gonna get you in trouble.
He's right. Nobody benefits,
and you'll just hurt her.
And there won't be a relationship
left to rebuild.
Don't you think
If you have to tell her,
at least wait till the timing's right.
And that's what deathbeds are for.
-Yeah, okay.
-All right.
Okay. Now, we just have to make sure
she doesn't find out some other way.
Did you think about the trail?
What trail?
From the woman
you did it with...
...to the woman you hope
never finds out you did it!
Always think about the trail!
I don't think there's any trail.
Chloe works with that guy, lsaac.
Isaac's sister is Jasmine, who works
at the massage place with Phoebe.
Phoebe is Rachel's friend,
and that's the trail! I did it!
"After applying the Waxine
and linen strips to leg"
Did that!
"Grasp the linen strip by its tab...
...and pull it off in one quick,
pain-free motion."
Was it not "pain-free"?
No, it was pain-ful!
My God, they should call it
"Pain-zine, now with a little wax."
The girls on the commercial
don't seem to think it's that bad.
Because their nerves are
deadened from being so stupid.
But you know, if you don't
believe me, please, be my guest.
Now are you glad we didn't start
with the bikini strips?
Chloe, hi.
Is this about me taking your watch?
-You took my watch?
-I'm sorry. I do that.
You keep it. Listen, did you
tell anyone about us?
I feel like it really isn't
anybody's business.
Exactly. So you didn't
mention anything to lsaac?
-I tell lsaac everything.
-You do? Of course you do.
Hi, lsaac.
You know, we haven't actually met.
You dog!
Yes, I suppose I am a dog. But see,
I happen to have a girlfriend.
Right. Rachel from the coffee place.
That's the one.
Listen, I don't want to hurt her.
I know. It doesn't matter
how much we love them.
Monogamy is too cruel a rule.
Listen, can you keep this
information to yourself?
No problem.
We gotta look out for each other.
We're the same, you and me.
Actually, no, we're not.
Yeah, we are.
No, we're not.
-Okay, we're not.
-Right.
But we are.
Fine. I just need to know
that you won't tell your sister.
I can promise not to tell her again.
Jasmine? We met at Phoebe's
birthday party. I'm Ross Geller.
You did a bad thing!
-Yes, I did.
-Very bad!
-Very bad.
-Very, very bad!
I'm agreeing with you.
Listen, did you happen
to tell Phoebe yet?
Please. Please don't.
I love my girlfriend very much
and I want to work it out with her.
All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
But you should talk to my roommate.
I told him, and he knows Phoebe too.
Who's your roommate?
Tell me you didn't tell Rachel about
me and the girl from the copy place.
I'm sorry.
Was I not supposed to?
-We're all right.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-We were just waxing our legs.
-Off?
For your information, this is a pain
like no man will ever experience.
Unless you've been kicked in an area...
...that God only meant
to be treated nicely.
Women just have a lower threshold
for pain than men, that's all.
I mean, come on,
it's just a little wax.
Oh, yeah? Come here.
Oh, that's mature.
So now I just pull it off?
That's right.
Just talk to me.
Please!
Talk to you?
I can't even look at you right now.
Nothing. Nothing.
-She said it was okay.
-What are they talking about?
-Just get away from me!
-I made a mistake, okay?
A mistake? What were you trying
to put it in? Her purse?
Where did he put it?
You had sex with another woman!
Oh, my God!
I knew something was wrong because
my nails didn't grow at all yesterday.
I guess they had a fight,
and he got drunk
You guys knew about this
and didn't tell us?
He has sex and we get hit
in our heads!
I want you to leave!
Just get out! Now!
I want to stay and talk about this.
All right. How was she?
-What?
-Was she good?
Don't answer that.
You said you wanted to talk about it.
Let's talk. How was she?
-She was....
-Awful.
-She was not good.
-Horrible. Nothing compared to you.
She was different.
Good different?
Nobody likes change.
-Just stop!
-What? Okay! Okay! Okay!
Should we do something?
Yeah. Never cheat on Rachel.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
I was disgusted with myself...
...and this morning
I was upset...
...and then I got your
message and I was so happy.
And all I wanted was to get her out
of my apartment
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Wait a minute.
What time did your
little friend leave?
Oh, my God. She was there?
She was still there?
She was in there when I was in there?
Listen, the important thing is
she meant nothing to me.
And yet she was worth
jeopardizing our relationship!
I didn't think there was
a relationship.
-We'd broken up.
-We were on a break.
That, for all I knew, could last
forever. That is a breakup.
You gonna get out of this
on a technicality?
I'm not trying to "get out"
of anything.
I thought our relationship was dead.
Well, you sure had a hell of a time
at the wake.
I don't think we should listen
to this anymore.
What are you doing?
We can't go out.
Why not? I'm hungry.
Because they'll know
we've been listening.
God! And to have to hear about it
from Gunther!
I ran all over the place trying
to make sure that didn't happen!
Oh, that is so sweet.
I think I'm falling in love with you
all over again.
We can go out. They have
other things to worry about.
We'll be fine.
Rachel, I wanted to tell you.
I thought I should.
And then Chandler and Joey
convinced me not to!
Wax the door shut.
We're never leaving.
It's Phoebe. Someone has to take
my 9:00 with Mr. Rehak...
... because it's 9:15 now,
and I'm not there.
None of this would've happened
if I didn't think...
...you were having sex with Mark?
All right.
Let's say I had slept with Mark. Would
you have been able to forgive me?
Yes, I would.
You'd be okay if Mark had kissed me,
and been naked with me...
...and made love to me?
If you knew that our hot, sweaty,
writhing bodies were
I would have been devastated...
... but I would still want
to be with you.
Because, I mean, it's you.
Come on, tell me what you're thinking.
I'm thinking...
... I'm gonna order a pizza.
Order a pizza, like...
... "I forgive you"?
Oh, man!
Pizza?
I like pizza.
Put olives on the pizza.
We could eat the wax! It's organic!
Oh, great. Food with hair on it.
No, not the used wax.
Because that would be crazy?
Could I get in on that?
Because I'm kind of hungry myself.
Fine.
Yes, I'd like to order
a large pizza.
-No anchovies.
-With extra anchovies.
That's okay.
I'll pick them off.
And could you chop some up
and put it right in the sauce?
You can have the last piece
if you want.
Well, I should think so.
You slept with someone.
They're gonna get through this,
aren't they?
Yeah. Come on, it's Ross and Rachel.
They've got to.
What if they don't?
You think I need a new walk?
What?
Well, I've been walking
the same way since high school.
You know how some guys walk into
a room and everybody takes notice?
I think I need a take-notice walk.
Are you actually saying these words?
What, now you're not even
talking to me?
Look, Rachel, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was out of my mind.
I thought I'd lost you.
How insane must I have been
to do something like this?
I don't cheat, right?
That's not me. I'm not Joey!
It's 3 a. m. They don't
know that I've come home yet.
You notice how they aren't
wondering where I am?
You know, people can be
so self-involved.
You know what? I'm not the one
that wanted that break.
You're the one that bailed.
You're the one...
...that ran the moment things
got rough.
-That's
-That's what?
-That is neither here nor there.
-Here we are...
...in a spot again.
What do you want?
How do you want to handle it?
You want to fight for us or bail?
Look, I did a terrible,
stupid, stupid thing, okay?
I'm sorry. I wish I could
take it back, but I can't.
I just can't see us throwing away
something we know is so damn good.
I love you so much.
No, Ross! Don't!
You can't just kiss me and
make it all go away.
It doesn't work that way.
It doesn't just make it better.
I think you should go.
What?
I really think you need to go now.
This morning you said there was
nothing we couldn't work out.
What the hell did I know?
There's got to be a way we
can work past this.
I can't imagine my life without you.
Without these arms...
...and your face and heart...
...your good heart, Rach, and....
I can't. You're a totally
different person to me now.
I used to think of you as somebody
that would never, ever hurt me.
Ever.
Now I can't stop picturing
you with her.
I can't. It doesn't matter what you
say or what you do.
It's just changed everything.
Forever.
This can't be it.
Then how come it is?
They've been quiet for a long time.
Maybe she killed him.
Let's go.
Is that your new walk?
No. I really have to pee.